Guide to the Lester R. Armstrong Photographs circa 1917-1957
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Chief Sugar Brown, Circa 1942 (Box 1, Folder 305)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Clown: Morales, Undated (Box 1, Folder 310)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Crowd scene, Undated (Box 1, Folder 311.28)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Elephant girl: Acevedo, Betty, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 307)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Escalante, Circa 1942 (Box 1, Folder 308)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Escalante, Melonga, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 303)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Marmolizo, Maurice, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 309.2)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Snake charmer: Helbing, Josephine, Circa 1941 (Box 1, Folder 311.06)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Ticket man: Meggs, Dan L., Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 302)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Weir, Betty, 1944 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 311.27)
- Circus: The Avalons, Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 270)
- Circus: Troupe: Walla Walla County Fair: Hicks, Jim, Circa 1946 (Box 1, Folder 311)
- [Circus], Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- City dump, Undated (Box 1, Folder 312)
- Clark: College Place, Undated (Box 1, Folder 313)
- Clark: Mr. and Mrs., 1946 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 318)
- Clark: Mrs Percy and daughters, 1951 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 317)
- Clark: Mrs. Percy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 314)
- Clark: Mrs. Percy and daughters, 1951 March 10 (Box 1, Folder 315)
- Clark: Percy and Family, 1951 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 316)
- Clearwater: Panorama, 1943 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 319)
- Clodius, Richard, 1950 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 320)
- Cloud, Circa 1944 (Box 1, Folder 322)
- Clouds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 323)
- Clouds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 324)
- Clouds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 325)
- Clouds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 326)
- Clouds, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 327)
- Clouds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 328)
- Clouds, 1940 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 329)
- Club: Sign local, Undated (Box 1, Folder 331)
- Club N.C.O: Farewell party: Lieutenant Creek, James W., 1945 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 330)
- Club: Catholic girls: Mrs. Adam Hunt, 1948 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 229)
- Club: Stamp, Undated (Box 1, Folder 332)
- Co-Op Farm Bureau Banquet: Official Group, Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Co-op: Lotzgesell, Henry, Undated (Box 1, Folder 359)
- Coal: Haulers, 1948 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 333)
- Coast: Scenery, Undated (Box 1, Folder 334)
- Coast: Trip, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 335)
- Coast: Trip, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 336)
- Coca Cola, Undated (Box 1, Folder 337)
- Cochran, Jub, 1953 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 339)
- Cochran, Jub (Glenn) Twins, 1953 June (Box 1, Folder 338)
- Cold springs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 340)
- Collard, Undated (Box 1, Folder 341)
- College: Pullman: Milky Way Dairy: W. E. Matson: Washington Farm Elect. Comm: Department of Agriculture and Engineering: State college: Pullman, Washington, 1950 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 342)
- College: Whitman, Undated (Box 1, Folder 343)
- Columbia River, Undated (Box 1, Folder 350)
- Columbia River: [Thrasher?] Ranch, Port Kelly, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Columbia River: [Thrasher?] Ranch, Port Kelly, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Columbia River: Near Chelan, 1941 August (Box 1, Folder 351)
- Columbia River: Twin peaks, 1949 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 349)
- Columbia River: Wallula Gap: Thrasher Ranch, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Columbia: Ice, Undated (Box 1, Folder 348)
- Combine: Moore, Luther, 1945 August 9 (Box 1, Folder 352)
- Companelli, Beverly, 1949 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 353)
- Comrie Motors: Miss Barnett with new Oldsmobile: Pendleton, Circa 1948 (Box 1, Folder 354)
- Conner, Clarence and family, 1952 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 355)
- Conner, Jack, 1947 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 356)
- Cook, Undated (Box 1, Folder 357)
- Cook, McCaw, Undated (Box 1, Folder 358)
- Coos Bay: Oregon, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1797)
- Copies: Advance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 360)
- Copies: Gleim, Dewey, Undated (Box 1, Folder 361)
- Copy: Ross advertising company, Circa 1948 (Box 1, Folder 362)
- Corn, Undated (Box 1, Folder 363)
- Cottonwood blossoms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 364)
- Coultas, Ethel: Family Group, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Coultas, Family group, 1947 June 15 (Box 1, Folder 365)
- Coultas, Mrs., Undated (Box 1, Folder 366)
- Crane, Eleanor, 1946 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 367)
- Creek, Circa 1941 (Box 1, Folder 370)
- Creek: Europe souvenirs, 1947 February 25 (Box 1, Folder 369)
- Crooked River, Oregon: Peter Skene State Park: Ogden, Circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 371)
- Cumming, Cecil: Ranch: Wallula, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Cummings, Cecil, Circa 1947 (Box 1, Folder 372)
- Cummings, Cecil, Undated (Box 1, Folder 373)
- Cummings, Cecil, 1947 September (Box 1, Folder 374)
- Cummings, Cecil, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Cummings, Cecil: Horse: Walla Walla County Fair, Circa 1947 (Box 1, Folder 375)
- Cummings, Cecil: Portraits, 1947 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 376)
- Cunningham, Corporate Robert L.: Walla Walla Air Base, Undated (Box 1, Folder 377)
- Cunningham, J.R., Undated (Box 1, Folder 378)
- Dagget, 1945 December 19 (Box 2, Folder 380)
- Daggett, Undated (Box 2, Folder 379)
- Dalton, Aerial: Show girl, Undated (Box 2, Folder 381)
- Daly, W. H., Undated (Box 2, Folder 382)
- Dam site: Walla Walla flood control, 1940 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 393)
- Dam: Arrowrock, Undated (Box 2, Folder 384)
- Dam: Coulee, Circa 1941 (Box 2, Folder 385)
- Dam: Coulee, Circa 1946 (Box 2, Folder 386)
- Dam: Coulee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 387)
- Dam: Grand Coulee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 388)
- Dam: Grand Coulee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 389)
- Dam: Grand Coulee: Dry, Undated (Box 2, Folder 390)
- Dam: McNary, 1947 April 15 (Box 2, Folder 391)
- Dam: McNary, 1953 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 392)
- Dam: Walla Walla flood control, Undated (Box 2, Folder 383)
- Dams: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2, Folder 394)
- [Dance: African American: Legion Hall], 1944 December (Box 2, Folder 395)
- Dance: Lowden, 1948 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 398)
- Dance: United Services Organizations: Square dance: Willam's wedding anniversary, 1945 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 396)
- Daniel, Doctor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 399)
- Daniel, Doctor, Circa 1942 (Box 2, Folder 400)
- Darkroom, Undated (Box 2, Folder 401)
- Darkroom, Undated (Box 2, Folder 402)
- Darkroom, Undated (Box 2, Folder 403)
- Davin, Betty, 1944 October 14 (Box 2, Folder 404)
- Davin, Virgil, 1948 April 29 (Box 2, Folder 405)
- Davis, David: Thirtieth Anniversary, 1949 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 406)
- Dawns, Carol: selected, 1953 May 23 (Box 2, Folder 441)
- Dawns, Carol: Unselected, 1953 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 442)
- De Vaughan, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1519)
- De Vaughan, Corporal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1520)
- Deegen, Doctor, 1949 August (Box 2, Folder 407)
- Deer, Undated (Box 2, Folder 408)
- Deer, 1948 April (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Delco light, Undated (Box 2, Folder 410)
- Deloney: Baby, 1946 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 409)
- Dental mechanic, Undated (Box 2, Folder 411)
- Depoe Bay: Coast trip, Circa 1949 (Box 2, Folder 412)
- Depoe Bay: Seascapes and agate column, 1949 August (Box 2, Folder 414)
- Depoe Bay: Street scene, Undated (Box 2, Folder 413)
- Depot: Accident, Undated (Box 2, Folder 415)
- Dick's: Waitress, 1946 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 418)
- Dickerson, 1947 June 22 (Box 2, Folder 416)
- Dickey, Undated (Box 2, Folder 417)
- Die Burke Building: 1st and main, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Diegel, Donna, Undated (Box 2, Folder 419)
- Diell, Nellie, Undated (Box 2, Folder 420)
- Dishes, 1940 November (Box 2, Folder 421)
- Display: Past corn flakes, 1947 March 9 (Box 2, Folder 422)
- Display: Windows: C.C. Anderson, Circa 1947 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Diving, Circa 1942 (Box 2, Folder 423)
- Dobbins: In studio: Noble, Circa 1946 (Box 2, Folder 424)
- Docks: Fishing: La Push, Washington, Circa 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1776)
- Doctor Nather, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1103)
- Doctors and Staff: Veterans Hospital: Walla Walla, 1942 March (Box 2, Folder 426)
- Dog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 428)
- Dog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 429)
- Dog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 432)
- Dog in lake, Undated (Box 2, Folder 430)
- Dog: K. Eilertson's, Circa 1951 (Box 5, Folder 1782)
- Dog: Buckley, Undated (Box 2, Folder 434)
- Dog: K. Eilertson, 1952 January (Box 2, Folder 427)
- Dog: Mac's, Undated (Box 2, Folder 431)
- Dog: On Nazi flag, Undated (Box 2, Folder 436)
- Dog: Rusty, Undated (Box 2, Folder 433)
- Dog: Verichrome, Undated (Box 2, Folder 435)
- Domanski: Passport picture: Man and wife, 1950 July 17 (Box 2, Folder 437)
- Douglass, William O.: Supreme Court Judge: Walla Walla Fair, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 439)
- Dowling, Jack: The great northwest truckbodies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 440)
- Dr. Geyer: Polled Hereford Bull, Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Drill teams, Undated (Box 2, Folder 444)
- Drilling Well, Undated (Box 2, Folder 445)
- Driveway, Undated (Box 2, Folder 446)
- Drum Majors, Undated (Box 2, Folder 447)
- Ducks, Undated (Box 2, Folder 448)
- Ducks, Undated (Box 2, Folder 450)
- Ducks: Boys feeding, Undated (Box 2, Folder 449)
- Ducks: City park, 1947 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 451)
- Duckworth, Weston, 1940 December (Box 2, Folder 452)
- Dunes: Sand, 1949 August (Box 2, Folder 453)
- Eagles dinner and club room, 1946 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 455)
- Eagles: Dinner, 1946 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 454)
- Eastern Oregon Canning Company: Boilers, Circa 1946 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Eastern Oregon: Corning Company, 1946 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 456)
- Eastland, Undated (Box 2, Folder 457)
- Eastman and Axtel: Veterans of Foreign Wars, Undated (Box 2, Folder 458)
- Eberhardt, Herman: Lenore, Idaho, Undated (Box 2, Folder 459)
- Ecola State Park, Oregon, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1806)
- Elephant: Circus, Undated (Box 2, Folder 460)
- Elk horns: Deer horns: Wired, 1948 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 462)
- Ellison, G., Undated (Box 2, Folder 463)
- Elsey, Ester, Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Elsye, Ester, 1948 February 27 (Box 2, Folder 464)
- Elsye, Ester, 1948 February 16 (Box 2, Folder 468)
- Engine: Caterpillar for Washington Chief, 1944 December (Box 4, Folder 1624)
- Engraving chart, Undated (Box 2, Folder 465)
- Engraving outfit, Undated (Box 2, Folder 466)
- Erwin, Gladys F.: Captain, 1951 August (Box 2, Folder 467)
- Everett's Cafe: Waitresses, 1947 May 4 (Box 2, Folder 469)
- Evous, Bertha, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1521)
- Ex-Brothertons, 1949 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 179)
- Excavation work, Undated (Box 2, Folder 470)
- Exhibit: Garden club, Undated (Box 2, Folder 472)
- Exhibit: Hobby club, Circa 1941 (Box 2, Folder 471)
- Exhibit: Military at armory: McCaw Hospital exhibit, 1943 December (Box 2, Folder 473)
- Exhibit: Picture, Undated (Box 2, Folder 474)
- Exhibit: Sudbury, Undated (Box 2, Folder 475)
- Experimental: File X, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Eye muscles, Undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Eye muscles: Doctor Rooks, Undated (Box 2, Folder 476)
- Fair, Circa 1949 (Box 2, Folder 497)
- Fair: A. M. Jensen Company exhibit, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 481)
- Fair: Agriculture booths, Undated (Box 2, Folder 477)
- Fair: Agriculture exhibits, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 480)
- Fair: Bergevin, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 482)
- Fair: Bicycle winner: Roberts, Danny;Ticket drawer: Joan Weaver, Larry Foster; Presented by Nick Gradwohl, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 478)
- Fair: Elmer Corkrim: Family on tractor at exhibit, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 483)
- Fair: Flower show, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 479)
- Fair: George Preston: Milton-Freewater, Oregon: Horse and girl, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 484)
- Fair: Grote Heifer: Aberdeen angus cow, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 485)
- Fair: Indians, Undated (Box 2, Folder 498)
- Fair: Junior Chamber Auction, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 486)
- Fair: Kong family, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 487)
- Fair: Mel Knight Insurance, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 488)
- Fair: Melcher: Ray Machinery Company, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 489)
- Fair: Nescafe display: Harry Gossner, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 490)
- Fair: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 491)
- Fair: Picture exhibit: Armstrong, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 492)
- Fair: Robinson's exhibit, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 493)
- Fair: Rownes, T. H.: Bee inspector: Bee exhibit, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 494)
- Fair: Walla Walla County: Bulls, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 502)
- Fair: Walla Walla County: Commercial booths, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 503)
- Fair: Walla Walla County: Falkenberg's, 1945 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 506)
- Fair: Walla Walla County: Indians?, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 504)
- Fair: Walla Walla County: Marine booth, Undated (Box 2, Folder 501)
- Fair: Walla Walla County: Miscellaneous, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 505)
- Fair: Walla Walla County: Parade, 1946 September (Box 2, Folder 500)
- Fair: Walla Walla County: Walla Walla County Farm Bureau, Undated (Box 2, Folder 499)
- Fair: Washington Co-operative Farmers Association, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 495)
- Fair: Wylie Monument works, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 496)
- Falkenbergs, Interior: Die Burke Building, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Falls: Along Columbia River, Undated (Box 2, Folder 507)
- Falls: Chelan Falls, Undated (Box 2, Folder 508)
- Falls: Palouse Falls, 1947 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 509)
- Farm buildings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 510)
- Farm Bureau: Walla Walla: H.L. Laurenz, editor: Farm Bureau News, 1948 January 8 (Box 2, Folder 511)
- Farmerettes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 512)
- Farming: Combine, Undated (Box 2, Folder 513)
- Farming: Horse plowing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 514)
- Farming: Tractor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 515)
- Farming: Truck, Undated (Box 2, Folder 516)
- Farming: Wheat, Undated (Box 2, Folder 517)
- Fehmer, Undated (Box 2, Folder 518)
- Fehmer, Helen, 1947 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 519)
- Fence rail, 1940 April 5 (Box 2, Folder 520)
- Fenchtown, First Annual Reunion, Undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Ferris Wheel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1679)
- Ferry: Emergency Columbia River, 1950 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 522)
- Ferry: Lyons: Near Starbuck, Washington, Undated (Box 2, Folder 523)
- Ferry: Lyons: Snake River, 1947 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 524)
- Ferry: Terminal at Megler, Washington, Undated (Box 2, Folder 525)
- Ferry: The Dalles, Oregon, Undated (Box 2, Folder 521)
- Fetter, Undated (Box 2, Folder 526)
- Figure studies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 527)
- Fine, Doctor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 528)
- Fine, Guy and Pearl: Clippings and photos of negatives in 529, 1951 February 3 (Box 2, Folder 530)
- Fine, Guy and Pearl: Fortieth Wedding Anniversary: Community Hall: Lowden, WA, 1951 February 3 (Box 2, Folder 529)
- Fire: 10th and Rose streets, Walla Walla, 1946 July 26 (Box 2, Folder 531)
- Fire: Wisemon: Wisemon's Service Station, 1947 November 12 (Box 2, Folder 532)
- Fires, Undated (Box 2, Folder 533)
- Fires, Undated (Box 2, Folder 534)
- Firestone, Beatty: Diner, 1948 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 535)
- Fish and Dam Conference: Columbia Basin Interagency, Undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Fish and Dam meeting, 1947 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 536)
- Fish, Tina: "A" Series, Undated (Box 2, Folder 539)
- Fish, Tina: Model, Undated (Box 2, Folder 540)
- Fish: Port: Fisherman's, Undated (Box 2, Folder 537)
- Fish: Sturgeon caught by Bob Musgrove, 1947 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 538)
- Fisher, Carl R., Undated (Box 2, Folder 541)
- Fishing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 542)
- Fishing, Salmon: Depoe Bay: Tradewinds, Undated (Box 2, Folder 545)
- Fishing: Depoe Bay: Pacific Trailers, Circa 1949 (Box 2, Folder 543)
- Fishing: Indian, Undated (Box 2, Folder 544)
- Flag, Undated (Box 2, Folder 546)
- Flenner, Undated (Box 2, Folder 547)
- Float: Rogers Canning, Circa 1941 (Box 2, Folder 549)
- Float: Rogers Canning: Pea Festival, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 548)
- Floats, Undated (Box 2, Folder 550)
- Floats, 1949 April (Box 2, Folder 552)
- Floats: Centennial: Parade, Circa 1936 (Box 2, Folder 553)
- Floats: Milton-Freewater Pea Festival: Queen float: Pacific Power and Light float: Ford Motors float, 1948 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 554)
- Floats: Pea Festival, Circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 551)
- Flohaug, Pat, Undated (Box 2, Folder 555)
- Flood: Columbia, 1948 June (Box 2, Folder 558)
- Flood: Columbia River, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 557)
- Flood: Touchet, Washington, Undated (Box 2, Folder 559)
- Flood: Walla Walla, Circa 1931 (Box 2, Folder 556)
- Flower, Undated (Box 2, Folder 560)
- Flower show: Whitney, Mrs. Vernon: Sweepstake winner, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 566)
- Flower: Bee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 561)
- Flower: Bee on rose, Undated (Box 2, Folder 562)
- Flower: Lilly, Undated (Box 2, Folder 563)
- Flower: Pansy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 564)
- Flower: Rose, Undated (Box 2, Folder 565)
- Flowers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 567)
- Flowers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 568)
- Flowers: In vase, Undated (Box 2, Folder 569)
- Flowers: Lilly, Undated (Box 2, Folder 570)
- Fogarty Creek: Oregon Coast, Undated (Box 2, Folder 571)
- Football: Wenatchee, Washington:Wenatchee High School, 1947 September 26 (Box 2, Folder 572)
- Ford: Tractor demonstration: Garage, 1945 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 573)
- Fraizer, Larry: Ground and aerial pea harvesting, 1950 July 12 (Box 2, Folder 574)
- Fraizer, Larry: New wheat harvester: Air base, 1950 July 18 (Box 2, Folder 575)
- Freedom Train, Walla Walla, 1948 March 30 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Freedom Train, Walla Walla, 1948 March 29 (Box 2, Folder 576)
- Freeman, Undated (Box 2, Folder 577)
- Freeman, Undated (Box 2, Folder 578)
- Freewater, Undated (Box 2, Folder 585)
- French, Doctor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 579)
- French, Doctor, 43998 (Box 2, Folder 580)
- French, Dr. A.D, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Frenchtown Reunion, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Frenchtown: Annual dinner, 1950 April 6 (Box 2, Folder 581)
- Frenchtown: Annual dinner, Circa 1944 (Box 2, Folder 582)
- Frenchtown: First annual meeting, 1948 March 21 (Box 2, Folder 583)
- Frenchtown: Second annual meeting, 1949 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 584)
- Friends: Business college, Undated (Box 2, Folder 586)
- Friends: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2, Folder 587)
- Friends: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2, Folder 588)
- Frolich, 1946 November 11 (Box 2, Folder 589)
- Fruit, Undated (Box 2, Folder 590)
- Funeral: Cochran, 1946 April 10 (Box 2, Folder 591)
- Funeral?, Undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Fur shop: Leading, Undated (Box 2, Folder 592)
- Gage, Frank: Children, 1946 September (Box 2, Folder 593)
- Gainer, Undated (Box 2, Folder 597)
- Gainer, Mrs. Alice, Undated (Box 2, Folder 594)
- Gainer, Mrs. Dorsey, Undated (Box 2, Folder 595)
- Gainer, Mrs. Dorsey, 1952 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 596)
- Gallo, 1947 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 600)
- Gallod, Tana Hoban, Circa 1944 (Box 2, Folder 601)
- Gallod, Tana Hoban, Undated (Box 2, Folder 602)
- Garage, Ford, 44046 (Box 2, Folder 605)
- Garage, Garland Coyle, 1946 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 606)
- Garden, Undated (Box 2, Folder 607)
- Garden: Stalker, 1946 June 20 (Box 2, Folder 609)
- Gardens: Spokane: Sunken, Undated (Box 2, Folder 608)
- Gardner's, Circa 1941 (Box 2, Folder 613)
- Gardner's: Easter window, 1949 April 9 (Box 2, Folder 611)
- Gardner's: Fall, Circa 1942 (Box 2, Folder 612)
- Gardner's: McGregor Display, 1947 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 610)
- Garland, Coyle: New Parts Depot, 1948 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 615)
- Garland, Kyle, 1944 August (Box 2, Folder 614)
- Garland: Coyle Motor Company: Exterior view and interior view, Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Garrison, Phyllis: Whitman: College delegate to the United Nations, 1948 September 26 (Box 2, Folder 616)
- Gas station: Washington Chief, 1945 July 22 (Box 4, Folder 1625)
- Gate Pole, Undated (Box 2, Folder 617)
- Gates Rubber Company: Denver, Colorado, 1950 January 28 (Box 2, Folder 618)
- Geese, Undated (Box 2, Folder 619)
- General Electric, 1947 January 23 (Box 2, Folder 620)
- General petroleum, 1947 September 23 (Box 2, Folder 621)
- General petroleum: Garland, Coyle: Garage, 1947 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 622)
- Gerred, Bob, 1942 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 623)
- Giana sisters, 1944 November 7 (Box 2, Folder 624)
- Gianni, Gloria, 1947 November 7 (Box 2, Folder 598)
- Gianni, Gloria, 1946 November 11 (Box 2, Folder 599)
- Gianni, Gloria, Undated (Box 2, Folder 603)
- Gianni: Wedding Anniversary, 1948 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 604)
- Gill, W. W., 1948 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 625)
- Girls, Undated (Box 2, Folder 626)
- Glads, Undated (Box 2, Folder 627)
- Glass, Undated (Box 2, Folder 628)
- Gleim, Dewey, 1944 June (Box 2, Folder 629)
- Gleim, Dewey, 1951 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 630)
- Glessing, Sergeant, Undated (Box 2, Folder 631)
- Goat, Undated (Box 2, Folder 632)
- Gobble, 1951 August (Box 2, Folder 633)
- Gobble, Marilyn: Birthday picture, 1951 January 23 (Box 2, Folder 635)
- Gobble, Virginia, 1951 September 2 (Box 2, Folder 634)
- Goulls, Undated (Box 2, Folder 650)
- Governor: Langlie: Walla Walla County Fair, Circa 1941 (Box 2, Folder 637)
- Governor: Sprague, Undated (Box 2, Folder 636)
- Graham, Lieutenant and girlfriend, 44153 (Box 2, Folder 638)
- Grand Coulee, Washington: Scenery, 1949 July (Box 2, Folder 639)
- Grand Tetons, Jacksons Lake, Grand Teton National Park, Wyoming, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1792)
- Granerson, Leola, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1522)
- Grasshopper, Undated (Box 2, Folder 640)
- Greib, Bert: Stud Horse: Walla Walla Fair, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 642)
- Griffin, Mr. and Mrs:, 1948 June 23 (Box 2, Folder 643)
- Griffith, Mrs., 1953 July (Box 2, Folder 644)
- Griner, Chas, 1943 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 645)
- [Groig] Family, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1810)
- Groups: Family: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Grudinksi, Family: Group, 1950 April 9 (Box 2, Folder 647)
- Guadalupe, California, Undated (Box 2, Folder 648)
- Gudgel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 649)
- Gunsmith, Undated (Box 2, Folder 651)
- Gunter, Doctor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 652)
- Guse, Helen, 1948 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 653)
- Guske, 1949 March 3 (Box 2, Folder 654)
- Haggen, Undated (Box 2, Folder 655)
- Hailstone, Oakley: Horse, Circa 1947 (Box 2, Folder 657)
- Hailstone, Oakley: Touchet, 1947 October (Box 2, Folder 656)
- Hamilton. Mrs., Undated (Box 2, Folder 658)
- Hammon, Dog team driver, 1940 September (Box 2, Folder 659)
- Hands, Heimbigner, 1945 December 12 (Box 2, Folder 660)
- Hanegan, Nelma C., 1946 June 17 (Box 2, Folder 661)
- Hansen and Smith: Telephone office, Undated (Box 2, Folder 662)
- Happy, Don, 1944 June (Box 2, Folder 663)
- Harbert, Mr. and Mrs. Calvin, 1951 November 29 (Box 2, Folder 664)
- Harding, Henry: Family: Group, 1950 April 9 (Box 2, Folder 665)
- Harding, Lena, 1943 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 666)
- Harding, Lena, Circa 1942 (Box 2, Folder 668)
- Harding, Lena, 1944 April (Box 2, Folder 669)
- Harding, Lena: Girl, Undated (Box 2, Folder 667)
- Harris Harvester Company, Undated (Box 2, Folder 671)
- Harris, Mrs., 1950 July 11 (Box 2, Folder 670)
- Harrison, Chas: Horse, 1956 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 673)
- Harrison, Peggy, 1952 February 21 (Box 2, Folder 674)
- Harrison, Peggy, 1951 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 675)
- Harrison, Peggy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 676)
- Harrison, Peggy, 1951 February 27 (Box 2, Folder 677)
- Harrison, Peggy: Alpha Chi Omega, 1952 January 29 (Box 2, Folder 672)
- Hart, Undated (Box 2, Folder 678)
- Hartwig, Undated (Box 2, Folder 679)
- Hartwig, Ken, 1950 April 6 (Box 2, Folder 680)
- Harvesting: Luther, Moore, Circa 1942 (Box 2, Folder 681)
- Hatchery: Walla Walla fish, Undated (Box 2, Folder 682)
- Haun, H. T.: Daughter, Undated (Box 2, Folder 683)
- Hawk, Undated (Box 2, Folder 684)
- Hawk Distributing Company, 1947 October 6 (Box 2, Folder 685)
- Hawk Distributing Truck, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Hawks: Dicky, 1945 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 686)
- Hawman, Arthur, Undated (Box 2, Folder 687)
- Hayes, W. H., Undated (Box 2, Folder 688)
- Haying, Undated (Box 2, Folder 689)
- Headley, Delmer Morrison, Undated (Box 2, Folder 690)
- Heater, Mr. and Mrs. Rem, 1951 April 1 (Box 2, Folder 692)